That's a short version explaining the sales feature.
So, everything comes here from the ICP selection of the company knowledge.
We have specific ICPs and those ICPs are dictating what are the job positions that we want to target.
For example, if I go in automotive, we could target the specific job positions here.
Having the ICPs defined, everything that the sales team needs to do is go in integrations
and connect their LinkedIn account.
Having their LinkedIn account connected, you go to target feature.
And in the target feature, you can see all the sales reps in the mission control here
that are assigned and you can click in auto-assign.
If you click in auto-assign, you can select the specific industries for this sales rep here.
And the specific region, and you save it,
the sales rep will have all the companies being instantly allocated to him, assigned to his auto engine.
So, the first thing in the target feature that we should do after this is most set is in the corner,
is clicking search and then you can see here the ICPs of the company in the top
and you're going to find for example investment banking, you're going to find a specific company listed.
You can check the revenue, their growth, and their website, LinkedIn, etc.
You select the companies that you want here and you click in track.
When you click in track, those companies will appear in the track feature.
And here in the track feature that is the home of the target function,
you can filter and check all the companies that you want.
For example, right now, I'm going to select Johannes and then I can see all the companies that are selected
according to the settings in auto-assign from Johannes.
And all these companies here, you can open them and you're going to see their shape, their revenue, their employees,
but the most important thing, the decision makers.
So, the decision makers of this company are already target with the specific ICP that we are looking for.
We have from the CFO to the legal officer, legal counsel, etc.
You can improve their shape in the ICP of the company or you can simply click in positions in the side,
select more positions and click in find people and then you will find people from this specific position.
Having all these companies assigned to Johannes, everything that Johannes needs to do is grow in your outreach.
Click in his profile.
This is the daily work of the sales representative.
Everything that he needs to do here is teaching the brain, the left side,
saving, learning lessons, how he wants to communicate,
uploading files from his previous successful conversations or Claude, GPT chats.
In the right side, he can improve his personality, his language, as well as his style, what to avoid,
how to build a relationship and etc.
In the middle, he has a message playground.
In the message playground, he can always generate post comment or first message, follow up and etc.
Selecting that, he can generate ideas.
So, those are dummy messages.
In the dummy message, the sales rep can just click in this like and tell,
I don't like this message because of this and that.
Or you can like and teach the brain that this is the sort of message that you actually like.
You can like or favorite to say, hey, this is my favorite type of message.
You can also do that after you edit the message and then you have a much more precise response, right?
Having the brain finished, everything that Johannes needs to do is,
according with his targets that are already coming here instantly from the target settings,
Johannes will response the outreach of those targets.
How this happened?
You can see that in the top you have settings, how many connections you want per day,
and if you want to have the warm outreach or not.
In the settings, by standard, we need to approve the message, right?
But in the future, after training the brain, the goal is that we select the settings for AI to send it automatically.
And how that happened? Very simple.
Every target that is assigned for the sales rep from the target list,
the AI will send a connection request.
You can see here that I just filter by connection and I will open one of the targets, right?
So AI send the connection request, check if they have connection with the sales rep, of course.
After sending the connection request, we're going to check one day, we're going to check another day,
and when the target accept the connection, we are scanning their posts and drafting comments for their posts.
So we are not just sending outreach random message in their inbox.
You can do that if you do the settings to do so, but we are first sending a comment in their posts.
Later, we are sending a message because we understand that there is much more conversions according with the past.
We notice that there is much more conversions if we warm up the lead commenting in one of their posts, right?
Okay, so what Johannes needs to do every day.
Johannes or the sales rep open the platform, clicking brain,
train the brain a little bit or go directly to the outreach.
In clicking outreach, you have the list of all the message that you can just approve,
dislike, give your feedback to generate a new one or edit.
When you approve the message or the comment, and you can see here, LinkedIn the message or LinkedIn the comment,
when you approve that, this is sent to the lead right away.
So then it's an easy way for you to every day be sending messages and sending comments according with our target audience
and warming up leads to build APIs.
If you click on Salesforce here, you can have a general overview of the content.
So in that moment, we have 2000 targets assigned for those two sales rep,
and everything that they need to do is just going the outreach and approve their message
and everything will run automatically.